Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
There's simply no way to shield
against every weaponized agent.
Instead. I can make
super-immune systems...
by strengthening
the human cellular response.
Banner. I know
where you're going.
But manipulating the immune system
is dangerous and stupid.
The president's science advisors
made it absolutely clear...
no human subjects.
David. I have wonderful news.
I'm gonna have a baby.
What's it gonna be?  Whoa. look at that.
Bruce. Huh?  Want a dinosaur?
Let's have a little fight.
You don't scare me.
That's a delicious eyeball.  Ooh. you're big
and green and scary.  I'm gonna run away.
Really. speaking of Cheryl.
guess what...
Bruce. you're hurt!
Jack hit him with the stick.
but Bruce wouldn't hit him back.
He just stood there. shaking.
It's okay.
Yeah. strange
he didn't make a peep.
Any other kid
would've wailed his head off.
That's Bruce. He's like that.
He's just so... bottled up.
The samples we found in your lab...
they were human blood.
You've ignored protocol.
You had no right
snooping around in my lab.
That's my business.
Wrong. Banner.  It's government business.
and you're off the project.
Attention. all personnel.
Fail-safe has been initiated.
Gamma decontamination
will occur in 30 minutes!
Evacuate immediately!
I repeat. evacuate immediately!
- Edith?
- David. what's going on?
- I gotta talk to you. Edith.
- Bruce. stay here.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to tell you
what has to be done!
David. please stop it!
No!
No! No!
Yes!
David! No!
Bruce.
Bruce. wake up. son.
Bruce. Bruce.
Another nightmare?
I don't know.
I don't remember.
Hi. Mom.
Already off to college.
Gonna miss you terribly.
I'll miss you too.
Please. come here.
Look at you.
Soon to be a great scientist.
I guess.
- I mean. who knows?
- I do.
There's something inside you...
so special.
Some kind of greatness.
I'm sure someday you're gonna...
share it with the whole world.
But as far as I'm concerned.
security oughta be...
Good morning. Dr. Krenzler.
Security oughta be beefed up.  In a
place like this you can't be too careful
Bruce!  Big day.
- Did you sleep?  I didn't sleep.
- I slept okay.
- Is Betty here?
- She's around.
I really gotta say. seeing you
in that stylin' head wear...
You're implying something
about my helmet?
You look like a massive nerd.
even around other scientists.
Can I just ask... Were you wearing
the helmet while she dumped you?
See. it protects my very
important brain. Harper.
Go prep the samples.
- Hey. I found you.
- Betty. hey.
I hate them.
-Wait. I just got here.  Who do we hate?
-The review board.
We have to make a
presentation on Tuesday.
And you're gonna make it with me.
You think I should?
Yeah. you're great with that stuff.
You start talking about microbes and
nanomeds. you sound almost... passionate
I'm sorry.
That was rude.
Look. nobody expects this
to be easy.
us working together
after being... so close.
We were close?
Look. if I could be more...
whatever. you know...
- I'm... just...
- Don't.
It's not your fault. really.
You're just a by-product...
of my inexplicable obsession
with emotionally distant men.
I'll get over us.
Good for you.
Anyway. I'm just really stressed
about this review.
If we don't get impressive results today.
we're gonna have a really hard sell come Tuesday.
Well. then. let's go be impressive.
Harper?
Ready when you are.
Let's hit it.
Are we passing inspection?
Safeties all going green.
Countdown's started.
Nanomeds released.
Four seconds.
Okay. nanomeds fully dispersed.
Okay. let's hit Freddie
with the gamma radiation.
Gamma exposure.
Nanomeds now active.
Nanomeds replicating cells on border.
It's working.
Cell copy to disassemble ratio
holding within one percent.
Imbalanced nanomed activity.
You wanna go to the review board
on Monday and tell 'em...
we've developed a brand-new
method for exploding frogs?
Yeah. I think maybe
there's a market for it.
I mean. what if there's a plague?
What have you had. Betty.
like. one beer?
I'm just sa...
I'm just saying. you know.
frogs start falling from the sky.
who do they come to?
We'd be world-renowned.
Make any parents proud.
I bet they would be.
They actually did
want me to be a scientist.
I mean. your birth parents.
Guess we'll never know.
I don't understand why you don't
want to find out about them.
They're dead.  They died before
I can remember anything.
Why do you always
come back to this?
Don't know.
I guess I figure there's more
to you than you like to show.
I guess there couldn't be any less
Right. So now we come
full circle back to that.
Nice work. Betty.
Betty.
- Glen.
- Hey.
Hi.
What happened
to your uniform?
Oh. I. uh...
I switched over.
I'm still working with your father. but...
Well. you know. the military's subcontracting
out all the most interesting work. and...
Can't argue with a paycheck.
I basically run
all the labs on the base now.
Oh.
Hey. you're uh...
you're looking good.
You're the genetics expert.
Ah. the good old college days.
So. how's business?
What do you want?
All right. I'll cut to the chase.
I've been hearing interesting things
about what you guys are doing here
Your little molecular machines
have some incredible implications.
How would you like to
come work for Atheon?
Get paid 10 times as much
as you earn now...
and own a piece of the patents.
You just have to say the word.
Two words: The door.
General?
Come in.
Talbot wanted you to see this. sir.
It's about a lab Atheon is targeting for
acquisition and removal to desert base
Why isn't it
going through N.S.C.?
It. uh. concerns
your daughter. sir.
Hi. Sorry.
Hey. what happened to Benny?  Is he
not working the night shift anymore?
Benny's dead.
I'm the new guy.
Oh.
Good to meet you.
Same.
- Let's try another.
Mmm. no. Stay here.
I look tired anyway.
Yeah. but you look great.
What's the matter?
It's these dreams. Doctor.
I keep having them.
and they're terrible.
Tell me about your dream.
Well. it starts...
it starts with a memory...
I think it's my first memory.
It's this image I have...
from when I was
maybe two years old.
Do you think
it's just a dream?
No. I think it's something
that happened...
when I was living at a desert base
with my father.
Anyhow.
the dream goes on and...
suddenly I'm alone.
That's terrible.
You know I'd never hurt you.
Hey there.
What's your name. darlin'?
Eh? What's your name?
Okay.
It's okay.
I gotta talk to you. Edith.
Bruce. stay here!
"C... T... G...
A... G."
Bruce.
My Bruce.
Good morning.
Glen dropped by.
What's he doing here?
You know. Dr. Krenzler.
you and I have never had the chance
to get to know each other properly.
Well. that's because I don't want to get
to know you. properly or improperly.
So leave.
Hey. no worries.
Let me give you a little heads-up.
There is a hairsbreadth
between friendly offer...
and hostile takeover.
I've done my homework.  The work
you're doing here is dynamite.
Think: Gls embedded with technology...
that makes them instantly
repairable on the battlefield...
in our sole possession.
That's a hell of a business.
Well. it's not what we're doing here.
We're doing the basic science for everyone
You know. someday
I'm gonna write a book...
and I'm gonna call it When Stupid Ideals
Happen To Smart. Penniless Scientists.
In the meantime. Bruce.
you will be hearing from me.
About Glen. I. um...
There's nothing to talk about.
Okay.
I just wanted to say. don't worry
about him... I'll handle it.
How?
I'm gonna call my father.
ask him to exert some pressure.
Last I heard. you and your father
weren't speaking.
Hmm.
Well...
I guess now I have something
to talk with him about.
I think this circuit's kinda fried.
I don't know.  Maybe you
anna come take a look at it
Okay. I'll be right there.
Aah!
The gamma's too high!
Bruce. I can't stop it!
Harper. get out!
Get out!
How's Harper?
He's all right.
You saved him.
I don't think he's coming back
to the lab for a while. though.
I don't understand
how this is possible.
You should be dead.
They worked... the nanomeds.
I mean. I feel great.
I feel like... I don't know.
They must have. like. fixed me.
Bruce. they've killed everything else
that they've come into contact with.
Are you sure
the doctor checked?
The doctor gave me
the full workup.
He wants to know where
he can get what I'm taking.
I'm a hundred percent.
More.
What do you mean?
Remember my bad knee?
Well. now it's my good knee.
Bruce. this isn't funny.
I was watching you.
You were gonna die.
and I was gonna have to watch you die.
Betty...
I'm sorry.
Really.
Hey. I'm not gonna explode.
Okay?
Yeah.
You should get some rest.
And I'm fine. Really.
I've never felt better.
Your name is not Krenzler.
It's Banner.
- What?
- Your name...
it's Banner.
Bruce Banner.
Bruce.
How did you get in here?
I work here now.
In the labs.
The late shift.
It keeps me close to you.
You always work so late yourself
with your friend Miss Ross.
No. no. Please. Please.
Let me.
You're not well.
You've had a terrible accident.
You're wondering
why you're still alive.
You're thinking
there's something inside.
Something different...
inexplicable.
I can help you understand.
if you'll let me.
If you'll...
forgive me.
Look. mister. I'm sure I have
nothing to forgive you for.
So perhaps you should leave now.
I'll be fine.
You must know.
You may not want to believe it.
but I can see it in your eyes.
So much like your mother's.
Of course.
you're my flesh and blood.
But then. you're something else too.
aren't you?
My physical son.
but the child of my mind too.
No.
You're lying.
My parents died
when I was a small boy.
No. no. that's not true.
That's what they wanted you to believe.
The experiments. the accident...
all top secret.
They put me away for 30 years.
Thirty years!
Away from you.
Away from our work.
But they couldn't keep me forever.
After all. I'm sane.
They had to admit it.
You see.
everything...
your extraordinary mind...
has been seeking all these years...
it's been inside you.
Now we will understand it.
We will harness it.
No. don't answer it.
It's Miss Ross again.
There's something you need to know
about her. Bruce. Something troublesome
Let me protect you from her.
No. Get out.
- Bruce...
- Get out!
Sit!
We're gonna have to
watch that temper of yours.
You sure you're okay?
Yeah. just glad to be out of bed
Got a message from my father.
He's coming to see me.
Your father?
When?
Lands in about an hour.
The funny thing is. he called me.
- Hi. Dad.
- Hello. Betty.
- Here. ma'am.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.  Sir?
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
Look. I'm gonna get right to it.
It's about Glen. isn't it?
He's been snooping around my lab.
Glen noticed some things.
asked me to make some inquiries.
Are you here to...
question me?
No.
We've turned up
some surprising things.
This Krenzler you work with...
you know who he really is?
How much do you
actually know about him?
I think the question is.
what is it
that you know about him?
- Well. right now. I'm not...
- Not at liberty to disclose it to me. Right
You know.
I think I was hoping that...
maybe this time you just...
honestly wanted to see me again.
- You've got this all wrong. Betty.
- Do I?
Yes. I do want to see you.
I really wishthat I
could believe you.
Everything...
your extraordinary mind
has been seeking...
all these years.
it's been inside you.
Hi. you've called Dr. Krenzler.
Please leave a message
and I'll call you right back.
Bruce. hey. Are you there?
Look. um.
I think I screwed up.
My father... It's like he suspects
you of something. I don't know.
- I was so impatient. like always.
I didn't hear him out.
I don't know. I...
I just think that they're planning
something with the lab.
So. um. uh...
Call me. Okay?
Bye.
- Betty?
Dispatch! Dispatch!
We have a 415 at the lab!
Send Berkeley P.D. Now!
Send 'em now!
Watch out!
Edith?
David. what's going on?
- I gotta talk to you. Edith.
- Bruce. stay here.
My Bruce.
Bruce?
There was some sort of explosion.
They wouldn't let us
into the building.
I was worried about you.
Well. I'm okay.
What happened to you last night?
I had the most vivid dream.
It was like being born.
Coming up for air.
Light hitting my face.
Screaming.
My heartbeat...
it was. like. boom...
boom...
boom.
Were you at the lab?
No.
But something...
And there was that man.
The one with the dogs.
Who?
That new janitor.
He said he was my father.
I'll get it.
My father.
My. my.
So this is the young Bruce Ban...
Krenzler.
I think you left something
in your lab last night.
Mitchell.
Escort my daughter outside.
I'll join her shortly.
I'd rather stay here.
Now. Betty.
It's okay.
I'll be fine.
Keep him under observation.
I'll be back.
- What?
- Your friend in there.
There's a good chance he's caught
up in some very bad business.
Unfinished business.
And I promise you. I'm gonna
get to the bottom of it.
You have my word
I'll make sure he's cared for.
But as of right now.
he is incommunicado.
And for the next
few days at least.
you're gonna stay away from here.
For your own good.
Okay. and that's for the new guy
on the night shift. right?
Great. Thank you.
I appreciate it.
Dr. Ross.
How unexpected.
Please come in.
I'm sorry to just show up
at your house like this.
Uh...
I came to ask you something that...
I really have no business asking
He told you?
He said you talked to him.
Oh.
Please sit down.
Bruce was at the lab last night.
He said that you were there too.
But he can't remember much about it
I need to find out what happened.
So. you want to know. uh.
what's wrong with him...
so you can fix him?
Cure him. change him.
My father's with the military.
He seems to think he's involved in
some kind of threat to national security
Mmm.
Your father. Ross.
You brought your father
down upon his head?
How little you understand.
Miss Ross.
and how dangerous
your ignorance has become.
I'm sorry.
Don't be sorry.
My son is...
unique.
That's why you can't relate to him.
And because he is unique. the world
will not tolerate his existence.
Will they?
But you...
you try.
don't you?
Yes.
And a very beautiful
woman like you.
your attentions...
can't be completely unwanted.
Can they?
No.
Not with eyes like yours.
watching expectantly.
lovingly.
But I'm afraid
we're both too late to help him.
There's nothing
I can do for him...
or for you.
Besides.
he's made it clear he wants
nothing to do with me.
His choice.
Now. if you'll excuse me. Miss Ross.
I have some work to do.
And don't worry about the dogs.
You'll be fine.
Just don't look 'em in the eyes.
Good-bye.
He gets released. and a month later
your lab is destroyed.
What a coincidence.
So you're not gonna tell me
where he is. are ya?
How many times do I have to tell you?
I'd like to help you. but I just don't know
You know who I am.
Right. Banner?
- Your Betty's father.
You're a high-ranking general.
- Let's cut the crap.
I'm the guy who had your father
tossed away. and a lot more like him.
and I'll do the same with you if I
feel so disposed. You understand?
If you had him tossed away.
then why are you asking me?
I don't remember.
I was always told my father was dead.
Don't play with me!
You were four years old
when you saw it.
When I saw what?
You were right there.  How could
anyone forget a thing like that?
What?
Oh. some more repressed memories.
Just tell me.
I'm sorry. son.
You're an even more screwed-up mess
than I thought you'd be.
Until we get
to the bottom of this.
your lab has been declared
a top-secret military site...
and you're not gonna get
a security clearance to get back into it...
or any other lab that's doing
anything more interesting than...
trying to figure out
the next generation of herbal hair gel.
One more thing.
If you ever...
come within a thousand yards
of my daughter again.
I'll put you away for the
rest of your natural life.
Dogs!
Go! Go get her!
And let nothing stand in your way!
Go!
Hello?
Bruce?
So. they think they can just
throw you away as they did me.
What's wrong with me?
What did you do to me?
I got a visit today.
A very unwelcome visit.
I'm afraid my hand is being forced
What did you do to me?
You so much want to know. don't you?
But I think no explanation
will serve you half as well...
as the experience.
In any case. I still don't
quite understand it myself.
If they'd only let me
work in peace...
Of course. my betters
would have none of that.
So you experimented
on yourself. didn't you?
And passed on to me... what?
An alteration. Genetic.
A deformity.
I guess you could call it that.
But an amazing strength too.
And now. finally unleashed.
I can harvest it.
No.
You'll do no such thing.
I will isolate it
and treat it myself.
I'll remove it and I'll kill it
before it does any real harm.
I'll bet you and your Betty
would love to destroy it.
But would you really
destroy part of yourself?
I don't think so.
And as for Betty.
I'm sending her a surprise visit...
from some four-legged
friends of mine.
You see. I managed to culture
some of your very own DNA. Bruce.
and the results are tremendous.
They're unstable. but very powerful.
What about my DNA?
Let's just wait and see what Betty
makes of the results. huh?
No. You're crazy.
I won't let you.
Get your hands off of me.
Talbot. what's this...
Inside. asshole.
I wanna talk to you.
Listen. my father's
going after Betty...
What makes you think you can go behind
my back and get Ross to cut me out. huh?
Listen to me!
Betty's in trouble!
You pathetic freak.
Betty's in danger.
I swear to you. she'll be killed.
I can state the obvious.
Something tells me you aren't in much of a
position to be making stupid threats to anyone
- Talbot.
- Yeah?
You're making me angry.
Oh. am I?
Ohh! Oh!
I got him! Open fire!
Bruce?
He sent these dogs. didn't he?
But I killed them!
My God.
It must be the nanomeds.
It must be the gamma exposure.
But we've never seen
any effect like this before.
No. Deeper.
The gamma just unleashed
what was already there.
Unleashed what?
Me.
It.
It's okay.
Shh. It's okay.
What were those animals?
My father sent them.
He is my father.
He wanted me to change.
He wanted me to change
into that mindless hulk.
Why would he want that?
Can you remember anything?
Is there anything
from when you were changed?
It was like a dream.
About what?
Rage.
Power.
And freedom.
Hello? Sir.
- Hello.
- Dad?
Betty! Are you all right?
I'm scared.
I need your help.
Where are you?
How are you?
Okay. I guess.
I think that somehow...
your anger is triggering
the nanomeds.
How could it?  We designed them
to respond to physical damage.
Emotional damage
can manifest physically.
Like what?
Serious trauma.
Repressed memories.
Your father grilled me about something that
happened to me from early childhood...
that I'm supposed to remember.
He did?
It sounded bad.
but... I honestly don't remember.
The thing that worries me...
is...
a physical wound is finite.
but with emotions.
what's to say it won't
just go on and on...
and start a chain reaction?
You know what scares me the most?
When it happens.
when it comes over me...
and I totally lose control.
I like it.
It's okay. I got you.
I'm sorry.
You'll be okay.
It's just to make you sleep.
Target down.
Target secure.
I'm going to take you someplace safe
Okay? Bruce?
Bruce?
Clear!
- Attention on deck.
- Carry on.
We're buried out here
in the middle of nowhere.
How long are you
gonna keep him sedated?
For the rest of his
natural life. if I have to.
You said I could trust you.
I'm your father.
You can trust me to do what I think
is right. not what you think you want
- He is a human being.
- He is also something else.
Suppose he gets out.
has one of his little mood swings...
in a populated area.
Yes. I'm aware of the potential danger.
I'm also aware that he saved my life.
Yeah. from a mutant
French poodle.
I'm indebted to him for that.
He also put three men in a hospital.
and Talbot's barely walking!
- What do you want me to do?
- I want you to help him!
- Why is he such a threat to you?
- Because I know what he comes from.
He is his father's son.
every last molecule of him.
He says he doesn't know his father
but he's workin'in the same
exact goddamn field his father did.
So either he's lyin'...
or it's somethin' worse. and he's...
What?
Predestined to follow
in his father's footsteps?
I was gonna say "damned."
Of course you were.
But I'm a scientist.
As a scientist. I believe we can figure
this out and he can be helped.
I know you do.
Look. whether you know or care.
I've got a lot of pride
in what you've done.
But this is too big for you.
Look. I know the government thinks
they have a weapon on their hands.
Otherwise. he'd be dead by now.
They can probe and prod
all they want.
and in the meanwhile.
just let me try to help him.
Nobody knows him better than I do
What did David Banner do to him?
Cover left!
Clear left.
Cover right!
What's happening here?
My hand.
You see. the strength
of my son's DNA...
combined with nanomed
reconstruction...
You see. I can partake
with the essences of all things.
Gonna have to ask you to...
put your hands up. pal. okay?
Nice and easy.
Do you really believe...
that I am separate from you?
Whoa!
Where am I?
You're home.
It's hard to believe
we used to live here.
I must have seen you or known you.
If only I could remember.
This is my old house. isn't it?
Let's go.
Please try.
What is it?
Nothing.
Really?
Damn it.
Okay. Betty...
what do you want to know?
What was in that room?
What are you afraid that I'll see?
See? There's nothing.
It's empty.
What do you mean.
I don't have access to him?
NSA has decided to turn over study
of the. uh... the threat to Atheon.
But you're head of the base.
I thought you were in charge.
But I don't set policy.
and I still take orders.
I can't believe Talbot
would go around me like this!
Oh. there's a lot of powerful people
that want in on this.
And money to be made...
lots of it.
You know the worst part
about all this?
When I had David Banner locked up
and sent that kid away.
I didn't give that boy a second thought;
he was just collateral damage.
Well. he isn't anymore. is he?
What can I do?
You can go home now.
I'd tell you to go and say good-bye.
but I've already been informed...
that for now all further contact
is out of the question.
Right.
Hiya. Bruce. How ya feelin'?
Grub okay in here for ya?
What do you want?
That's a good question.
See. I need your cells to trigger
some chemical distress signals.
You know. so you can turn
a little green for me again...
and I can carve off
a piece of the real you.
analyze it. patent it.
make a fortune.
Do you mind?
I'll never let you.
I'm not sure you've got
much of a choice.
Come on. Bruce.
Aren't you feeling a little angry?
After all. you've only got me to play with now
that Betty's dumped you and gone back to Berkeley
You're lying.
You know. for me
this is a win-win situation.
You turn green. and all these guys
come in and kill you...
and I perform the autopsy.
You don't...
And I mop the floor with you...
and maybe by accident
go too far and break your neck.
Bad science. maybe...
but personally gratifying.
Come on. Bruce!
Let's see what you got.
Never.
You know. consciously
you may control it.
but subconsciously.
I bet that's another story.
All right. let's jump-start
those brain waves.
Bruce.
- My dear Miss Ross.
Welcome back.
There are two guards
right outside.
You don't have to worry.
I'm not angry with you. Not anymore.
What do you want?
It's over for me now.
I know that.
And soon it'll be over for Bruce.
That's why I've come to you...
to ask you if you could
persuade your father.
as a man. as a father himself.
that if I turn myself in now.
peacefully...
and before
he puts me away forever.
that he would let me see my son...
for one last time.
Could you do that for me?
It's out of my father's hands now.
I understand.
He's a puppet now.
I don't blame him.
You shouldn't.
You should blame yourself
for what you've done to your son.
And what have I done
to my son. Miss Ross?
Nothing. I tried to improve
on the limits in myself.
Myself! Not him!
Can you understand?
To improve on nature.
My nature!
Knowledge of oneself!
It's the only path to the truth...
that give men the power
to go beyond God's boundaries!
You know what's beyond
your boundaries? Other people.
All you've given Bruce is fear.
Fear of life.
Fear?
Perhaps. Miss Ross.
And loneliness too.
Yes... I feel them both.
But I have lived...
completely once.
I was so much in love.
and she so much wanted a baby.
My baby.
I could tell
from the moment she conceived...
that it wasn't a son
I had given her...
but something else.
A monster. maybe.
I should have put a stop to it
right then.
but I was curious
and that was my downfall.
And as I watched this tiny life unfold.
I began to imagine the horror of it.
and my curiosity was replaced...
with compassion.
But they took away
my chance to cure him.
Your father threw me out.
- What are you doing?
- I remember that day so well...
every moment. every sensation...
walking into the house.
the feeling of the handle
of the knife in my hand.
I knew I was doing a father's work.
fulfilling a father's mercy.
David. please stop it! No!
David. no!
Talk to me! Listen!
But then she surprised me.
- No! No!
David. no!
It was as if...
she and the knife...
merged.
No!
You cannot imagine...
the unbearable finality of it.
And in that one moment...
I took everything that was dear to me...
and transformed it into nothing more...
than a memory.
Bingo! That must be some
jumbo nightmare he just had.
Okay. do it now.
Start the enzyme extraction.
Sir. negative on drill penetration.
Damn it. drill him harder! Give him full RPMs
Come on. Holeman! Come on!
-Should I neutralize?
-No. I can't do anything with goop. c'mon on
- All right. put him to sleep.
It's not stopping him!
Ready room. send in
our containment team.
Non-lethals only.
I repeat. non-lethals only.
I must have a sample of him.
Sir!
- Jesus!
- Hit him with the foam.
Deploy containment foam.
Talbot. talk to me.
Under control. General. I'll let
you know if we need you.
Unacceptable.  Unseat your
asses down here immediately.
I want a full-court evacuation now.
I'm shutting you down.
Lockdown.
-Didn't you hear what the general said?
-I said lockdown!
Clear! I need a sample of him!
Take it easy there. buddy.
This might give you
a bit of a sting here. Bruce.
- Fall back! Fall back!
- Clear your weapon! Clear it!
- Give me the M2.
- So long. big boy.
Clear!
Lockdown the entire facility immediately
Target's still moving towards blue level
- Evacuate the main hall.
Send in backup. heavy weapons.
Issue general quarters.
Set firing lines left and right!
Heavy weapons. go. go. go!
Contamination. sir.
System readings are redline.
Data's on backup power supply.
Incoming!
-Shut down all power to the main hall
-Sir?
Show him the way out.
We'll fight him outside.
Driver. stop.
Gunner. traverse left!
Traverse left!
Clear back! Clear back!
Mr. President.
I have some bad news. sir.
Let's have it. General.
I've briefed the president on Angry Man.
I assume that's what this is about.
It is. ma'am. I'm requesting
a National Command Authority override.
Angry Man is unsecure.
I need everything we have at my disposal
in order to stop his movement.
You're expecting
civilian casualties. General?
Not if I can help it. ma'am.
Consider it done.  Keep us posted.
Contact Goodman Control.
Patch data to the assets.
Contact H.Q.
Have them initiate
an immediate evacuation...
in vicinity of grid coordinates
653-216...
Confirm that the area
has been cleared.
Confirm area cleared.
H.Q. Confirms area cleared.
Assets on-line. sir.
Gentlemen. it's time to dig in.
I want this target
stopped in his tracks.
Jesus.
Mayday! Mayday! Ah. shit!
Tango Four is down. Have C-SAR
respond to our 20 ASAP.
We're okay. but. damn it. get him
off us before he tears us apart!
I've got no shot.
Do you have a clear line of fire?
Watch it. Tango Flight.
Break left! Break left!
Tango Three. pull back and set up
for a Hellfire shot.
Hold your fire till we draw him off.
Tango One is hot. Gun wazzed.
Roger. Going hot. Guns ready.
Engage at will.
Tango One. pull back!
Clear my line!
Tango Flight. clear back.
I've got him painted for Hellfire.
Roger that. Tango One clear.
Take the shot.
Tango One. Tango Three.
I have contact.
Holy shit! He's got my missile!
Mayday! Mayday!
We're hit! We're going down!
Give me a head count.
Tango Three. give me a sit rep.
Our kite's busted up.
but we're okay.
Tango Flight. do you have
eyes on the target?
Tango One. I have him in the rocks.
Salvo all. Turn it into a parking lot.
T-bolt. your parking lot is ready.
We're bingo for fuel and ammo.
R. T.B.
T-bolt. this is Goodman Control.
Be advised. target not destroyed.
He's on the move again.
Damn!
I've got it.
It appears he's heading home.
Launch fast movers.
Have them intercept and engage.
Hello?
Betty. Bruce got out.
He's headed your way...
and probably right for you.
How far from the base are you?
I'm already here.
They're taking his father in now.
That's all good news.
Stay there. Betty.
Legend One rolling in hot.
Legend Two breaking offleft.
I think I can come back around
for a gun attack.
Acquire a clear target.
Fire at will.
Increase altitude.
Civilian aircraft in vicinity.
Pull up! Pull up!
You're headed for the bridge!
I can't pull up! I can't pull up!
Okay. you've got him now. Take him
on a ride to the top of the world.
Let's see what the thin air
will do for him.
Initiating afterburner.
I'm passing flight level 600.
This is out of my envelope.
Hang in there. Legend.
I can't maintain.
He's all over my aerodynamics.
He'll lose consciousness before you.
Nine-fifty. I can't hold it.
I'm pulling back!
Puny human.
Contact. He's in the water.
All units. weapons hot.
Let's not take any chances.
You are cleared to fire
on target. Legend.
- Dad?
- Betty?
We don't have a choice.
I have to destroy him.
But you can't.  You will only fuel
his rage. and you will make him stronger
It's you he's coming for.
You know that.
Then let me go to him.
Please.
Just give him a chance to calm down
This area has been declared
restricted airspace.
All aircraft are ordered
to clear the airspace immediately.
Echo. One-niner. Weapons are hot.
Target acquired.
Waiting your orders to engage.
Repeat. waiting
your orders to engage.
Command code yellow.
Hold for authorization.
All units. hold your fire.
This is T-bolt to all assets. You have
direct orders to hold your fire.
I repeat. hold your fire.
Echo. One-niner. Roger that.
Go go. go. go. go. go!
Hold your fire until my command!
Engine 24 to command.
We are in position now.
You found me.
You weren't that hard to find.
Yes. I was.
Let's take a walk.
That's the deal. gentlemen.
He stays on this base...
until we get the final word from C-3
on how to dispose of him.
In the meantime. ifhe does
anything but sit there in that chair.
we're gonna turn on the juice
and he'll be incinerated immediately.
We've established a
200-yard perimeter. sir.
If we deploy the electromagnetic array.
there should be no collateral damage.
Here they come!
I'm doin' this for you. Betty.
But one way or another. we're
gonna have to prepare for the worst.
I should have killed you.
And I should have killed you.
I wish you had.
I saw her last night.
Saw her face.
Brown hair.
Brown eyes.
She smiled at me.
She reached down and kissed my cheek
I can almost remember a smell.
Almost like desert flowers.
Her favorite perfume.
It's my mother.
and I don't even know her name.
It's all right. son.
You go ahead and cry.
Go ahead and cry.
Cry. Crying will do you good.
Don't touch me!
Maybe once you were my father.
but you're not now
and you never will be.
Oh. is that so?
Well. I got news for you.
I didn't come here to see you.
I came here to see my son.
My real son.
The one inside of you.
You're nothing but a superficial shell.
a husk of flimsy consciousness...
ready to be torn off
at a moment's notice.
You can think what you like.
I don't care. Just go!
No. son. Listen to me.
I found a cure.
For me.
My cells can transform too.
absorb enormous amounts of energy.
But. unlike you. they're unstable.
Son. I need your strength.
I gave you life.
Now you must give it back to me!
Only a million times
more radiant. more powerful!
- Stop it.
- Stop? Stop what?
Stop what?
Think about all those men out there
in their uniforms...
barking and swallowing orders.
inflicting their petty rule
over the entire globe!
Think of all the harm they've done!
To you! To me!
To humanity!
And know this...
that we can make them...
and their flags and their anthems
and their governments...
disappear in a flash!
You in me.
I'd rather die.
Oh. that's your answer?
Then indeed you shall die...
and be reborn...
a hero... of the kind
that walked the earth...
long before the pale religions
of civilization...
infected humanity's soul!
Go!
Stop your bawling.
you weak little speck
of human trash.
All right... I'll go!
- You just watch me go!
- Hit it.
- Hit it again!
We can't. sir. There's no power. Some
kind of counter-electromagnetic field.
Move in and assault the target.
Move in!
Move. move. move!
Sir. I've located them on radar.
Pear Lake.
Call up the task force.
Yes!
That's right. Keep fighting.
The more you fight.
the more of you I take.
Strange. We're reading a phenomenal
drop in temperatures there.
But simultaneous radiological activity.
They're absorbing
all the ambient energy.
Sleep now. Bruce. and forget forever.
Struggle no more...
and give me all of your power.
You think you can live with it? Take it!
Take it all!
Oh. yes! Yes!
Take it back!
It's not stopping!
Gentlemen... release.
Gamma charge away.
- Mwah!
- Sweet dreams.
- Hello?
- Betty. is that you?
- Hi. Dad.
- I'm glad I caught you.
- I'm glad you called.
- Thanks.
Look. Betty... you and I...
well. we both know that Bruce
couldn't have survived that blast.
But... well. you know...
- What is it?
- Well. you know.
The usual loonies.  Seein' things.
Only now everything's green.
Right.
Look. uh...
if by some chance
he did survive...
and he should try to contact you.
try to get in touch.
you'd tell me. wouldn't you?
No... I wouldn't.
But you know as well as I do.
I wouldn't have to.
I mean. my phones are bugged.
my computer's tapped.
I'm under surveillance.
I'll tell you. though.
that if he were alive.
I'm the last person
I would want him to come to...
because... as much as I miss him.
I... I... loved him.
I. um...
Yeah.
I'm sorry. Betty.
I am so sorry.
I know you are.
Si.
Let's take a walk.
# You operate and motivate
on synthetic fuel
# You're Mother Nature
and an atom bomb
#As long as you're kept
full of pretty bodies
# Your little secret
will be safe with me
#Around again. insane again
#It comes again and sets me free
#So set me free. set me free
# 'Cause I think you need my soul
#Set me free. set me free
# You kept a lock and pulled a rise
with one thing in mind
#But analyzing
everything that you see
#But now I did it all. I did a little
#Now I wanna take you down with me
#Around again. insane again
#She comes again and sets me free
#So set me free. set me free
# 'Cause I think you need my soul
#Set me free. set me free
#So set me free. set me free
# 'Cause I think you need my soul
#Set me free. set me free
#So take me down. take me
#Down. down. down. down
# Take me down. take me down
#So take me down. take me
#Down. down. down. down
# Take me down. take me down
#So set me free. set me free
# 'Cause I think you need my soul
#Set me free. set me free
#So set me free. set me free
# 'Cause I think you need my soul
#Set me free. set me free
#So set me free. set me free
# 'Cause I think you need my soul
#Set me free. set me free
#So set me free. set me free
# 'Cause I think you need my soul
#Set me free. set me free
#So set me free. set me free
# 'Cause I think you need my soul
#Set me free. set me free
#Not real
#That's a wrap!
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm